{
    "id": "0b6b45577e2147f9b189cc2cfa22f4e9",
    "title": "Find the mistake – prepositions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b012cdcbc6684538a05579bb729cb86c",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is that cute girl ..................................... the fifth row?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a big spider ..................................... the ceiling.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Granny is arriving ................................... the 30 train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "As there was no room on the bus, we got .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t throw food ...................................... the animals.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We should arrive ..................................... Smith’s in time for dinner.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She lives in a flat ................................... the third floor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did you do .................................... the weekend?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He can run 1000 meters ................................. about four minutes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I met her .................................... a cold afternoon in winter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}